ALYSSA WILLIAMS

alyssajanelwilliams@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/ajwilliams12/en https://github.com/alyssaw90

Profile

Upon graduating in 2012, I started my career in physical therapy. Working in physical therapy clinics I gained experience working with patients and health insurance. During this time I started thinking about how technology could change and improve the health care and health insurance industry. I started to teach myself how to code, and now I am in the General Assembly Web Development Immersive Course.

Skills

- Languages: JavaScript, Ruby, HTML, CSS
- Frameworks: Node.js, Express JS, Rails, AngularJS, Sailsjs
- Database Tools: SQL, PostgreSQL, Sequelize, ActiveRecord
- Authorization: Bcrypt
- Testing Frameworks: RSpec
- Other: Git/GitHub, Heroku, jQuery, AJAX, JSON, Bootstrap, Microsoft Office Suite

Experience

GENERAL ASSEMBLY, WEB DEVELOPMENT IMMERSIVE COURSE 2014- PRESENT

It is a 12 week intense and immersive course that teaches different languages and frameworks. During this course we are learning JavaScript, Express JS, Node.js, Ruby on Rails, AngularJS, and more. Also we 3 individual and group projects are completed during the course.

DIRECTOR OF REHAB ASSISTANT, INFINITY REHAB 2014

Complete schedules daily for therapy team, keep compliance/HIPAA regulations up to date, attend meetings, help prepare director for meetings, keep therapy team organized, listen/attend to patient and therapist concerns, order office/equipment supplies

EXERCISE SPECIALIST, MARRAN PHYSICAL THERAPY 2013-2014

Starting patients, set up patient rooms, help patients with exercise and rehab, set patient up on different modalities, laundry, pick up clinic, help at front desk, order supplies

PHYSICAL THERAPY AIDE, PROLIANCE SPORTS THERAPY 2012-2013

Starting patients, set up patient rooms, help patients with exercise and rehab, set patient up on different modalities, laundry, pick up clinic, help at front desk

Education

UNIVERSITY OF PORTLAND, PORTLAND, OREGON — LIFE SCIENCE B.S., 2012